<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>Prathamesh Daily Journal</title>
    <subtitle>Prathamesh daily journal where I share my experiences</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2025-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Andrew tate workout!</title>
        <published>2025-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/02-09-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/02-09-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/02-09-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was fucking awesome.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did 50 Andrew Tate burpees. Killed me, brother. It was so intense but I felt way better after. Slightly more productive than the streak of unproductive days I’ve been on.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listened to some Tate motivation too. Sometimes it works. It’s not fully right, not fully wrong—it’s a paradox. People say motivation is useless, but at the initial stage it can give you that spark to start.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Truth is, you only get accurate answers by applying thesis, anti-thesis, synthesis. That’s how you win in life. Not by complaining.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck yeah. Stay hard. Today I’ll beat the shit out of my current character. He’s pulling knives—I’ll pull guns and kill him. And step into my future self.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for intense workout&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for not dying while doing andrew tate workout lol&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The best revenge is success.</title>
        <published>2025-09-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-09-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/1-9-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/1-9-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/1-9-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was that family event I used to dream about. I always pictured pulling up in a car, laptop in the backseat, iPhone in hand. But the date came and I didn’t even have a mobile of my own.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We arrived earlier than everyone else since we’re closer family, and I was just sitting there with nothing. That’s when it hit me—if you don’t take action, dates come and go, years pass, and nothing changes. Dreams stay dreams. Beliefs stay beliefs. Action is the only thing that makes them real.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, my hair is too long now. Tried growing it out but it just makes me look dull—like some tribal guy. Chubby cheeks too since I haven’t worked out in 2 weeks.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One more thing I noticed most of the teens my age there were talking nonsense, just people and events. None of them had the capability I have.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best revenge is success. Nice cars, the lifestyle, and pulling up for real.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Unproductive day and a sherwani</title>
        <published>2025-08-31T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/31-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/31-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/31-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was another really unproductive day. Feels like I’m stuck in this loop of unproductivity.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out of nowhere I got tired and tried on a sherwani. Thinking of wearing it on the cultural event in my locality on the 1st of September.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s hope for the best. I want to look like one of the best out there at the event.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The world doesn’t deserve a good person like me</title>
        <published>2025-08-30T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/30-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/30-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/30-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today I finally went on the trip that kept getting canceled for days.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly, it wasn’t that good. Nothing new, just the same old place. After that went for groceries with dad and fixed a few things. Decent day overall.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I noticed something. I’m way too friendly. Always quick to offer a handshake, and people just ignore it. Feels stupid. I need to be rougher, tougher. The world doesn’t deserve a good person like me.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for realising this fact&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for the fact that i will be more produtctive from next time&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Today was wasted..</title>
        <published>2025-08-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/29-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/29-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/29-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today I basically wasted my whole day planning a trip that got canceled.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realized my friends are just stingy and not worth giving so much attention to. I need to stop. No point.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll make new friends. better, richer, smarter ones. No worries.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, today was wasted. Shamefully wasted.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am grateful for the realization about my friends.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am grateful for the new friends I will make.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Unproductive Waiting Game</title>
        <published>2025-08-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/28-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/28-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/28-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was unproductive.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a plan to go somewhere nice but it got canceled. I noticed something about myself. I get really excited when we make plans and then just sit around waiting for the time to come, without doing anything productive in between.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to fix that. And I seriously need to start using my own to-do list app again. It’s been days since I was at my most productive.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for my leg bing fine and not broke&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>A Messy Day of Pizza, Soda, and a Scooter Mishap</title>
        <published>2025-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/27-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/27-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/27-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was pretty unproductive.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a random plan to go out. I was already busy buying Ganpati, got exhausted, was about to sleep, then friends showed up. Ended up getting some pizza and tried a cold drink for the first time in my life. Hated it. The fizz on the tongue feels terrible, not my taste at all.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main thing three of us were on one scooter, and my foot hit the silencer of a parked bike while we were speeding. No idea if the silencer broke, but the hit was bad. I couldn’t walk properly after that.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Friends, Business, and Bad Advice</title>
        <published>2025-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/26-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/26-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/26-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was really unproductive.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some kid keeps coming over to play video games and I just can’t work when he’s around.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talked with my friend too and realized his whole paradigm is trash. He was saying I should do freelancing and hire a developer to build my app. That’s like working harder just to please your wife. Makes no sense.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to dream about having friends who talk business. Now I do, but their business paradigm is way behind mine. So maybe with them I should just talk about other stuff, not biz.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, I explained my view and even offered to teach him the fundamentals of the right paradigm.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Bike Rides, Night Shifts, and a Broken To-Do List</title>
        <published>2025-08-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/25-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/25-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/25-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today I rode the bike once. Feeling pretty confident with it now. That was basically the whole day.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dad had his once-a-month night shift. Not even a real night shift, just go there and sleep. Weird system, but whatever. You don’t fight the system, you go with it, take the profits.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall a good, productive day. But I’m slipping on my to-do list. Some bugs messed it up and I stopped using it. Need to fix that fast.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>A Quiet Sunday</title>
        <published>2025-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/24-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/24-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/24-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Not much happened today. It was a quiet Sunday.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>I am a bike guy</title>
        <published>2025-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/23-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/23-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/23-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Woke up late today.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day was good but not productive. No run, nothing. Just went with dad to an empty space and practiced riding the bike. Turns out my only issue was the clutch. Once I got that right, things clicked. Rode for a good half hour. Skill leveled up.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later my uncle started asking about my future, what his son is doing, extra classes, tuitions, all that usual Indian stuff. In my head it was like fuck you. I’m not breaking my paradigm. I know my path, and I’m not into that shit. I’m on the right side.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for bikee&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Dad is negative </title>
        <published>2025-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/22-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/22-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/22-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was kind of negative but also had some positive parts.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morning started off good. Dad was in a really positive mood, his teeth situation also felt positive. At night too, got into a deep positive mindset.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tried a bit of biking today. Didn’t care about whether I knew how to or not. Just went on the road and did it. No theory, no overthinking. Best way to learn is by doing. That’s it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for good paradigme&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>New ISP </title>
        <published>2025-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/21-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/21-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/21-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was kind of a bad day, but decent in terms of learning.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got my internet changed. The guy came late, said he’d be back in 30 minutes, showed up after 3–4 hours. Classic. Around 7:40 some insanely loud bike went past the highway—you can still hear it half a kilometer away.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learned about X (Twitter) today. Always thought it was just random noise, but the algorithm is actually deep. It runs on conversations, engagement, conversions. It’s not just posting, it’s social. Makes sense now why it works the way it does.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had some new inputs today, felt good. Evening was fine. But I keep having this fear of writing tweets. Like if I post, I want it to be perfect. Inner me says “just do it, give it 100%.” But then I stall. Limiting belief.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, good learning day overall.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for WIFI&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for learning&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>My friend</title>
        <published>2025-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/20-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/20-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/20-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Got some sunlight, went for a run, and reconnected with a friend I hadn’t talked to in a long time. Found out another friend has typhoid and is in the hospital. Also planned with my friend when we’ll go out, eat pizzas, just chill.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Washed my bean bag so I can sit in the sun like the main character of a movie. Because I am the main character of my movie.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realized I’ve been less selfish lately. Need to bring that back. Selfishness is power. I earned 16,000 rupees at 16, online. Who the fuck does that? That’s value. I just forget it sometimes.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m at the wrong time and wrong situation, but that’s on me. I’m responsible. For waking up early. For what I watch. For taking action instead of watching endless courses. It’s all on me.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also got a notice about some financial security issue linked to my dad. Nothing huge, could be cleared by selling 3–4 gold rings. Hopefully the guy’s uncle pays since he got some government funding. Whatever. Small lesson: stay out of unwanted trouble, even if it’s relatives. Main characters don’t get dragged into other people’s mess.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for talking to my friend&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful that I didn&#x27;t caught typhoid&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>I fucked up my to do list </title>
        <published>2025-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/19-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/19-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/19-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today wasn’t anything special.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up, made a list, did some bug fixing. My to-do list template got messed up and I lost it. Kind of killed my flow. Unproductive, but still my mistake. I could’ve handled it better.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Sam Ovens’ course I picked up something: to experience good days you need bad days. Without dark, there’s no light. If everything was just light, you wouldn’t even know what light is. That’s why God throws bad days at us—so we can actually feel the good ones.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also realized how people treat universities. They were built to make people educated and capable of earning, but now they’ve been turned into some religion. Everyone follows it blindly, thinking it’s the ultimate truth, while ignoring other ways of learning. And the same thing happens in business. People start to be independent but then take VC money and end up slaves to it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indie hacking feels like the only clean path. Building independent. Like Telegram. That’s who I want to be. No VC.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for healthy life&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for a change&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>No funding at all is needed!</title>
        <published>2025-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/18-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/18-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/18-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today felt like one of the best days.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started using my own web app properly and instantly saw so many impractical things. That alone is going to make the product sharper and more valuable.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom got sick today. She was on fast. Dad had a blood test.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, everything feels like it’s moving in the right direction. Like things are pivoting toward more happiness.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did stress about funding for a bit. But honestly, at 17 or 18 you don’t need a funded startup. Just build something independent, get financial freedom, buy some cars, enjoy youth. After 25 maybe build a “real” SaaS, apply to YC, go bigger.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now it’s simple: my parents are getting older, they’ve never seen the world, and that’s priority one. Get independence, travel with them, good dinners, marriage. Then think YC.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overthinking never teaches you anything. Doing does. Who knows if this app will even need funding. You figure that out by acting, not sitting.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t care about billions right now. 5–10 million is enough to live luxuriously off interest alone. That’s doable independently. The only focus is ticking off my goal list. Nothing else.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for going in right direction&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for the indi community&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>This is the End, the glowing future I see </title>
        <published>2025-08-17T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/17-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/17-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/17-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;today was one of the happiest days of my life.
woke up late.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after so many days there was sunlight. i was excited. then clouds came. now i get why people call them sadness.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;did my own stuff. used my webapp. got a lot of self review. already fixing things.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;later the sun came back. i went out, took 15 min sunlight. i was shaking and chilling from it. the happiness i felt seeing the green nature with sunlight was unreal. best sunlight experience in all my 17 years.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;at night dad came home happy with fruits. we went again to buy more fruits.
boom. perfect day.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for Sunlight !!!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for Sunlight !!!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for Sunlight !!!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for Sunlight !!!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for Sunlight !!!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for Sunlight !!!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Saw my dad smile after months</title>
        <published>2025-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/16-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/16-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/16-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was a good day. Dad’s dental work got done. Problem gone. He’s feeling much better now, able to eat properly. Said the happiness he felt today was mind-blowing. Ate a full stomach. I could see it on his face. That’s what I’m working for. His happiness.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still need money, obviously, to set the future. But moments like this matter more.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Went to the dentist, got it done, came back. Decided I’ll start using my own web app. I haven’t been using it myself, and that’s the only way I’ll actually improve it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the best days. At night I had some anxiety before sleeping, worried if things will work out or not. Pretty common when you’re on this kind of journey. Then I just slept.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for dad&#x27;s smile&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for taking actions&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for goods days are starting&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>I am Indi</title>
        <published>2025-08-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/15-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/15-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/15-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;15th August. Independence Day. Means nothing to me now. Not in school anymore. Honestly, it’s more like independence for me, I always hated going there just to watch everyone do their own little flag hoisting. Why not have one flag for the whole town and be done with it?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today’s “independence” was from online payments. Spent 6–7 hours fighting with Airtel to disconnect my Airfiber. Easy to install, hell to uninstall. Calls, emails, customer care loops. Got it done through email. Billing stopped. Not paying a single rupee. They said prepaid, acted like postpaid. Scam. Not giving them a penny.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New connection coming. Offline payment. No more begging others to pay for me. Grateful for that.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did some running. No gym. Morning dad was happy, night he was down because of dental pain. Showed him videos from top dentists in India. He chilled out after that. He just trusts the wrong people sometimes, and wrong info can wreck your life. Always trust the right professionals. Not random broke people with opinions.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People here have crab mentality. Tell you you can’t fix something. Plant negativity in your head. But when you compare their words to what the pros say, facts, logic, real examples, you know who to believe.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day wasn’t productive. Didn’t track my stuff. But one big problem is gone. Dad’s mood is better. That’s enough for today.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for decentralization of power&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for disconnection&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for TOP G DR of YT&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Can&#x27;t maintain my standards</title>
        <published>2025-08-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/14-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/14-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/14-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Woke up at 7.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whole day was a hassle. Thought Wi-Fi would get cut today. No money, no docs ready for a new connection. Dad gone for work.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spent half the day stressed. Kept wondering why the internet is still working even after the due date. It shouldn’t.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was worried they’d force me to pay or sue me. Later found out they won’t really do anything bad if I don’t pay. Stress gone.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did some bug fixing. Worked on bills. A bit of workout. Walking. 50 min run.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not a super productive day. Most of it went into worrying about the Wi-Fi. It matters a lot to me. I fought to get it. I deserve it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for running internet&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for my dad support&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Thermostats theory is G</title>
        <published>2025-08-13T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/13-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/13-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/13-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up
applied thermostat theory again got my thermostat page on desktop with highs and lows graph
look at highs, set as standard, do whatever it takes to keep it&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;yesterday did every task on my list no guilt no wasted time
idea is you’re not who you want to be you’re who you accept to be
like I accept shorts and wife beater at home but not outside
same with money a millionaire accepts millions per month as normal I haven’t lived that yet so my standard is different&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;gym done meditation done walking done&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;wifi payment problem no online option no mobile basically no internet
solution is new provider with offline payment
past few days harsh people told me to get lost when I asked for help topping up
dad refuses online payments because broke people told him it’s unsafe
rule 1 never take advice from people who aren’t experts
let them live in their mindset I’ll live in mine&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;been staring at my 1080p screen so much it feels like my real life is inside it
believe in myself so much it might be delusional but I know hard work in the wrong direction is useless
you have to iterate like the rat experiment where happy rats chose normal water over drugged water
environment changes everything&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that’s it for today tomorrow thermostat theory again&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for wifi&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for my mindset&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am sorry for my dads mindset and people around him&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Thermostats theory</title>
        <published>2025-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/12-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/12-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/12-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;don’t remember when i woke up today
got my extension done for the web app
works fine but UI is messy, will fix later&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;no instagram at all today
gym done
15 min run done
no meditation today
got my sunlight&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;end of the day went to the rooftop
walked while listening to samoans&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;learned about thermostat theory
idea is you’ll do whatever it takes to maintain your standard
you’re not who you say you are, you’re who you accept to be
if you’re productive, healthy, meditating, running
you’ll fight to keep that momentum
that’s what momentum is to me&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;my version:
make a graph of your highs and lows
highs are productive days, healthy eating, no addictions
lows are lazy days, binge watching, skipping workouts
set your highs as the standard
when you drop even slightly, fight to get back up&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;same for money
if your standard is 8k&#x2F;month, you’ll do anything not to go below it
hard to jump from 8k to 80k, but easy to keep 8k
thermostat theory explains that&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;first thought it was bullshit
then understood it and realized it’s actually useful
like songs or ideas you think are trash at first
then they grow on you&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;biggest takeaway
don’t dismiss things just because you don’t understand them
my society does that
but i choose to question, learn, and think differently
that’s what makes you exceptional&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;good day overall&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Snow ball effect</title>
        <published>2025-08-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/11-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/11-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/11-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up at 7
slept again and woke up at my default 9 a.m.
really need to change that&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;decent day
productive day&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;noticed my skin glowing after so many days
had this golden brown kind of glow
not dull at all
depends on lifestyle
past week i’ve been running 15 mins daily
gym almost consistently
15 mins meditation
10–15 mins sun bath when it’s sunny
cold showers only, no hot ones&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;all that made my skin glow like crazy
yesterday’s run felt so easy
felt like i could do 30 mins instead of 15
had energy, had the glow, felt great&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;maybe my health was up because of a really good week
not in work terms, but in health terms
didn’t make sacrifices there&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;genetics wise, yeah my family has belly fat issues
but i don’t want to blame genetics
i’m responsible for where i’m at
truth is i eat a lot of carbs because i can’t afford protein right now
but in future i’ll set things so i can eat greek yogurt, cheese, organic eggs every day
low carbs, more nutrition, no excuses&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;overall, day was very good
ticked a lot of tasks off my list
great day&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for glowing skin&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for late night walk in cold weather&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for energy&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Your now is your mind 6 months ago</title>
        <published>2025-08-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/10-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/10-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/10-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up late again
it’s sunday so yeah woke up pretty late&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;was kind of productive today
fixed a bug and did some copywriting for my landing page
that’s it for my project work&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;day was a bit exhausting
i usually do 15 minutes of running at home but today i couldn’t
barely managed 6–7 minutes
maybe because i did four squat till failure sets before running
still don’t think it should have affected me that much&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;sweated a lot, sat under the fan, speaking into the mic for this journal&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;nothing special today
felt like going out but it was already night and i don’t like cycling at night&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tomorrow is monday
i feel tomorrow is gonna be one of the most productive days
money loves speed
i’ve been hearing it for a long time, but now i’m applying it
when i feel lazy i just think “money loves speed” and get to work&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the results you have now are from the info you fed your mind in the past
so to change your future, change what you consume now
that’s why i don’t surf youtube and i’ve blocked instagram
don’t want negativity or envy
just want to build, fix my life, and keep going&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for 9 ratri&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for productive day&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Block Instagram NOWWWWWWWWWWWWWW</title>
        <published>2025-08-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/9-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/9-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/9-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up late today
it’s saturday so yeah woke up around 10 a.m.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;nothing much happened
not a productive day
spent the whole day fixing just one bug in the share activity feature of my web app
that’s it&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;went to the dentist with my dad
he’s gonna get root canal done for 2 teeth
completely normal stuff&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;one good thing though
i blocked instagram from my dns so it’s not accessible on my pc now&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;decent day but unproductive&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The growth</title>
        <published>2025-08-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/8-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/8-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/8-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;Today was solid.
Fixed a bunch of bugs that were pending.
Started working on a big feature — feels like it could actually help people like me.
Pretty hyped to see how it turns out.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hit the AI usage limit for coding today.
Tried a little hack with two accounts.
Still ran into the Kiro AI error even after the wait time.
Hope they fix it soon.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did some meditation.
Quick workout.
15-minute run.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing crazy.
Just a clean, productive day.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for dentist&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for healthy teeth&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Almost died, but it was a good day!</title>
        <published>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/7-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/7-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/7-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up around 8
did 5–6 tasks
felt better after a few low days&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;friend’s birthday
went out, had pizza and cake
almost got hit by a bus
fun day&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;been home too long
finally stepped out
felt normal&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;nothing deep
just a good day&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you know it&#x27;s a good day
when you almost died
but somehow still ended up eating pizz.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for hilarious day!&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for the weather&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Implemented landing page</title>
        <published>2025-08-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/6-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/6-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/6-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up around 6:40
sat in the living room, almost dozed off again
reminded myself it&#x27;s not the bed, so got up and started working&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;finally integrated the landing page into the app
was overthinking it for weeks
turns out it was a simple fix
moved the landing page into vite, that’s it&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after lunch, took a nap
later did a bit more work&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;neighbor’s kid came again
but didn’t play this time, his mom warned me
so just stayed chill and did my stuff&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;in the evening, a friend came over
we talked about AI and online stuff
he doesn’t have a laptop or working phone
told him to just start Instagram theme pages on mobile and figure it out from there&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;coaching has started for 11th
subjects are finally a bit logic-based
feels good&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;no fights at home
just a simple steady day
landing page finally done
felt good&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Midish day</title>
        <published>2025-08-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/5-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/5-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/5-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;woke up at 6
again put 30 min timer
woke up at 6.30
then again 7
anyway finally woke up at 10&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after that just did my things
tried to implement the landing page into my main web app
nothing major
not a really good day&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;had a nap for 2-3 hours after lunch
then went out for some bhakarwadi
came back
did some small work on our project&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then that neighbor&#x27;s kid came to my home
he’s the kid of that famous doctor who lives nearby
played with him for 2-3 hours
went to store
got some biscuits for him&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after that left home for a bit
but there was a blackout
so yeah&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;overall
not much work
just a lot of random timepass with that kid
maybe some oxytocin
wasn’t a bad day tho&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;no clashes in house
just a decent day&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for peace&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am greatful for lots of money.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Bad day.</title>
        <published>2025-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/4-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/4-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/4-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;so today i tried to woke up at 6
but i was in that half-sleep drunk kind of state
so i just put a timer for 30 mins
then again 30 mins
then again
and then slept without even putting timer
and finally waked up at 10&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after that did some house chores
important ones
did that
then little bit of workout
nothing special&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;today was really stressful bro
one of the worst day of this whole month
had a fight with someone
not gonna mention who
but yeah it was really irritating&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so i just went to that lush green spot of my town
just to find some peace
got my mtb repaired so
took the cycle there
called my friend too
we did a nice walk
talked
i did some cycling too
so like a good one hour of movement&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;also did some chest workout later
little bit of push-ups
nothing big
just felt like doing it&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;on the way back i saw one guy with his dog
i just asked what’s the name of the dog
he said ruby
nothing else
just felt like socialising a bit&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then came back home
again had some clashes
again stress
mind is completely gone
momentum lost
mindset empty
no productivity
did literally nothing today&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and yeah
when you have fights in your environment
your mind just doesn’t want to work
you don’t feel like doing anything&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but i’ll wake up early tomorrow
and start again from zero
that’s it&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am grateful for asking dog&#x27;s name&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am grateful for the nice sunset view&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am grateful for nice walk&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The day I unfucked my mind and project</title>
        <published>2025-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/3-8-2025/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/3-8-2025/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/3-8-2025/">&lt;p&gt;okay so today was actually one of the best days i&#x27;ve had in weeks. not because everything was perfect but because i finally made a move that felt right. like really fucking right.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;here’s what happened&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i made a mistake. or wait maybe not a mistake. i learned from it and if you really learn something from a mistake it ain’t a mistake anymore right. there’s this line from a rapper i follow something like “the one who learns from defeat isn’t actually defeated.” that line hit me hard. because it perfectly sums up what i went through.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so a few weeks back i decided to move my whole project yeah nexttap, the actual core app from vite.js to next.js. and at the time i thought i was being smart. i was like “yeah man, this’ll be good for long-term scalability blah blah.” but yesterday i realized what a dumb move that was.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it all started because i found this landing page template online. it was made for next.js. instead of converting that small template to vite which would’ve been a small fix, i went full psycho mode and decided to move the whole fucking project to next.js. like changing the entire car just because one tire had a puncture. what the fuck was i thinking&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;three weeks went down the drain. three. fucking. weeks.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and i don’t even know next.js that well. i was literally just feeding shit to the ai like “pls fix this,” “pls migrate that.” no real thinking, no real building just endless cycles of npm run build → error → fix → build again → error again. it was a loop of insanity. no productivity. just headaches.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and honestly i’m not a dev. i’m a fucking entrepreneur. i build stuff to solve problems not to over-engineer a tech stack that no one even asked for. like bro i don’t even have real users yet. what the hell am i doing worrying about “long-term scalability” that’s like worrying about marriage when i haven’t even been on a date.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so yesterday i did the right thing. the smartest move in weeks.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i ditched the migration&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;thanks to github and some luck i got my original vite.js code back. i recovered everything. and i made the final call i’m sticking to vite.js. no more next.js bs. it works it’s fast it’s easy and it’s enough. i’m not here to impress other devs. i’m here to build and ship shit that helps people. that’s it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and for the landing page yeah i’ll convert that next.js template into vite manually. way easier than converting my whole app. hundreds of times easier. makes actual sense.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this was a huge mindset shift&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;people love to complicate things especially marketers and devs. they want their job to look rocket-science-level hard but in reality most of it is pretty simple if you just stay focused on the outcome. solve the problem get paid. that’s the game.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so yeah yesterday marked a new direction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i’m not wasting time anymore chasing the “perfect tech stack” i’m sticking with what works. i’m gonna focus on shipping on launching on getting real feedback on solving real shit. that’s how i’ll win.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am great full for solving this migration prob.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am great full for learning from my mistakes.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>It was a really good day!!</title>
        <published>2025-08-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/it-was-a-good-day/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/it-was-a-good-day/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/it-was-a-good-day/">&lt;p&gt;Brother, today was one of the best days of my life man. Literally the best day of my whole fucking life.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to the sunset point of my town, it’s like a small valley-type place where there’s this lush, never-ending green forest.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I saw one man who was releasing a caught snake from a jar from the top of the valley.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was with my friend Sahil, who&#x27;s been my bro since forever.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were 2 other people there watching the snake release too.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a really good conversation with one of them. The other one was busy talking to his buddy.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a good handshake with that guy, we talked, and my friend had a good handshake too.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
Then we went to MIDC, which is kinda like sunset point, lush and green, but it’s an industrial area.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had some snacks there, and the tank was empty. Boom.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were in the middle of nowhere, in an industrial area, it was getting dark.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
Somehow we managed to push the scooter and got to the highway. Sometimes it started, sometimes it didn’t.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But then there was this school teacher we used to have. We didn’t want to pass his house while pushing the scooter like some helpless people. Man, just no.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
It was really funny for us. We were like, no matter what, we are not crossing his house like this.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we decided to take a chance. We started push-pulling the scooter, back and forth, hoping that one small drop of petrol hits the engine and somehow we cross that 100-meter road.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
And boom, scooter started.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were really excited to cross the road and that house.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We fully accelerated the scooter. He was riding it btw. He gave full throttle and boom...!!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We stopped right in front of the house we didn’t want to cross like that.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And bro we were laughing so much. Like so much. I can’t even explain it in text. Shit was mad funny.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It started.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
It accelerated well.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
But but but... it just decided to stop &lt;em&gt;right&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; in front of the house.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lol.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we hit the highway. My dad saw me. He was sitting outside an Indian-style dhaba talking with the owner.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
He showed me his hand like, &quot;Hey son, come here.&quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to him and he’s like, &quot;Here’s 50 rupees, take it.&quot;&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
I explained what happened and he said, &quot;Go get some petrol in a bottle.&quot;&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
But the problem was the petrol pump was far.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we met a friend. He was like a lifesaver.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
I took the bottle from the dhaba and the 50 rupees and said to my friend, &quot;Bro, let me go. It’ll be awkward if I stay here with my dad.&quot;&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
I’m not really that open with my dad like that.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I made my friend get off the scooter and explained why I didn’t like the idea of both of them going and me staying.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
He didn’t really understand what I was feeling, but anyway, I talked with him. Had a good talk.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got the petrol from the pump.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I came back, fuck... we had relatives over. Two people, around our age, like 20s, and they were ready to help.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out of nowhere, we had options now.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly one of the relatives says, &quot;Isn’t there petrol in your scooter boot?&quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sahil checks the boot and goes, &quot;Oh fuck...&quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We already had petrol there.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We fucking pushed that scooter like pyramid slaves.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I had 50 rupees petrol in hand and more already in his boot.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck. And lol.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We literally did this pushing shit for like 3 to 4 KM straight.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we finally reached home. He dropped me at my place. And we just sat back and enjoyed what the heck happened to us today. Really fun day tbh.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And brother, we also talked about our other brother. He’s not with us anymore, like he’s out of town for studies.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
But now he lives with completely different people. Like degenerates. And we saw such a big change in his behaviour, his thinking, his whole mindset.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
It’s not the same person we were friends with before.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He changed.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also realised today how badly the people around you can affect your mindset if they’re not the right kind of people.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, good day overall.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I gave my bike (cycle) to the repair shop today. It was like 4 to 5 km of cycling in the morning.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this 10 km of physical travel, my body is fully exhausted today, bro. Like totally done.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m grateful for a good day.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
I’m grateful my bike will be repaired.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
I’m grateful for bhakarwadi.&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
And I’m grateful for this one good day… after so many lonely days.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used chatgpt for fixing the grammar but tone and the story is OG.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Things Are Geting Hard</title>
        <published>2025-08-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2025-08-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/things-are-getting-hard/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/things-are-getting-hard/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/things-are-getting-hard/">&lt;p&gt;guys life is getting hard hope i will achive my dreams no matter what i do.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I watch fan spinning and ovethink about my life&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My dad is getting retired soon like in few months ..&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to make it before this happens&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or we will face a big financial crisis&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is now or never&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made this blog with zola and it took the whole day but..&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can use Kiro without bugs now.. and got this dashing claude 4 sexy ai!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can use this to convert my project from vite to next without any prob at all&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;lets see it tomorrow today I hit my usage limit, thats why but if this was not the case then brother&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;there is no tomorrow&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Placeholder Text 1</title>
        <published>2023-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/placeholder-1/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/placeholder-1/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&amp;hellip;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
        <published>2022-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/usefulls/markdown-syntax/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/usefulls/markdown-syntax/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Zola content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Kita theme.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Shortcodes</title>
        <published>2022-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Prathamesh
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/usefulls/shortcodes/"/>
        <id>https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/usefulls/shortcodes/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://prathameshh8.github.io/Journal/usefulls/shortcodes/">&lt;p&gt;The Kita theme providers multiple shortcodes.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never heard of shortcodes? See &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.getzola.org&#x2F;documentation&#x2F;content&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Zola documentation&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; for more information.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;mermaid&quot;&gt;Mermaid&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To use Mermaid in your page, you have to set &lt;code&gt;extra.mermaid = true&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; in the frontmatter of page.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;title = &amp;quot;Your page title&amp;quot;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;[extra]
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;mermaid = true
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then you can use the &lt;code&gt;mermaid()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcodes like:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% mermaid() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;graph TD;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;A--&amp;gt;B;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;A--&amp;gt;C;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;B--&amp;gt;D;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;C--&amp;gt;D;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be rendered as:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;mermaid bg-inherit&quot;&gt;
  graph TD;
A--&amp;gt;B;
A--&amp;gt;C;
B--&amp;gt;D;
C--&amp;gt;D;
&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, you can use code block inside &lt;code&gt;mermaid()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcodes and the code block will be ignored.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The code block prevents formatter from breaking mermaid&#x27;s formatting.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% mermaid() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;```&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#d08770;&quot;&gt;mermaid
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;sequenceDiagram
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    participant Alice
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    participant Bob
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    Alice-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Hello John, how are you?
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    loop Healthcheck
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;        John-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Fight against hypochondria
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    end
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    Note right of John: Rational thoughts &amp;lt;br&#x2F;&amp;gt;prevail!
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    John--&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Alice: Great!
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    John-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Bob: How about you?
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;    Bob--&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Jolly good!
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;```
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be rendered as:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;mermaid bg-inherit&quot;&gt;
  
sequenceDiagram
    participant Alice
    participant Bob
    Alice-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Hello John, how are you?
    loop Healthcheck
        John-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Fight against hypochondria
    end
    Note right of John: Rational thoughts &amp;lt;br&amp;#x2F;&amp;gt;prevail!
    John--&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Alice: Great!
    John-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Bob: How about you?
    Bob--&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Jolly good!

&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;admonition&quot;&gt;Admonition&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;admonition()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcode displays a banner to help you put notice in your page.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use the &lt;code&gt;admonition()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcode like:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% admonition(type=&amp;quot;tip&amp;quot;, title=&amp;quot;tip&amp;quot;) %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#a3be8c;&quot;&gt;`tip`&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; admonition.
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The admonition shortcode has 12 different types:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(68, 138, 255, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;note.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      note
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;note&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;note&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(0, 176, 255, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;abstract.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      abstract
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;abstract&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;abstract&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(83, 211, 230, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;info.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      info
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;info&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;info&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(0, 191, 165, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;tip.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      tip
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;tip&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;tip&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(0, 200, 83, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;success.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      success
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;success&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;success&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(100, 221, 23, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;question.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      question
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;question&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;question&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(255, 145, 0, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;warning.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      warning
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;warning&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;warning&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(255, 82, 82, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;failure.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      failure
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;failure&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;failure&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(0, 176, 255, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;abstract.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      abstract
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;danger&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;danger&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(255, 23, 68, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;bug.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      bug
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bug&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;bug&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(101, 31, 255, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;example.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      example
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;example&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;example&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
 &lt;!----&gt;


&lt;div
  class=&quot;my-4 flex flex-col rounded-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)]&quot;
  style=&quot;--admonition-bg: rgba(159, 159, 159, 0.1)&quot;
&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;flex items-center rounded-t-lg bg-[var(--admonition-bg)] p-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div
      class=&quot;mx-2 h-4 w-4 text-[0px] [background:var(--url)_center_center_no-repeat] dark:invert&quot;
      style=&quot;--url: url(.&#x2F;icons&#x2F;quote.svg)&quot;
    &gt;
      quote
    &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;quote&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;pl-4&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;quote&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; admonition.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;gallery&quot;&gt;Gallery&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;gallery()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcode is very simple html-only clickable picture gallery that displays all images from the page assets.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#x27;s from &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.getzola.org&#x2F;documentation&#x2F;content&#x2F;image-processing&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Zola documentation&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{{ gallery() }}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;not-prose flex flex-wrap gap-2&quot;&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;01-zola.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;01-zola.25af19fa02482a0b.png&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;02-zola-manet.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;02-zola-manet.0cad2873502bda50.png&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;03-zola-cezanne.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;03-zola-cezanne.2637293cc0f9ca40.png&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;04-gutenberg.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;04-gutenberg.e156bb46a4925a33.jpg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;05-example.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;05-example.89a127c589096583.jpg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;06-example.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;06-example.cc9c6c223f960c32.jpg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;07-example.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;07-example.c8114c1ffd3dcfda.jpg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&#x2F;Journal&#x2F;usefulls&#x2F;shortcodes&#x2F;08-example.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;rounded-lg&quot; src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;prathameshh8.github.io&amp;#x2F;Journal&amp;#x2F;processed_images&amp;#x2F;08-example.8f6405859d5efe66.jpg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  &lt;!----&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;inline-svg&quot;&gt;Inline SVG&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;inline_svg()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcode is used to embed SVG images directly into a webpage, rather than including them via an &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;img&amp;gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; tag.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use the &lt;code&gt;inline_svg()&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; shortcodes like:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% inline_svg() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;![Van de Graaf canon](Van_de_Graaf_canon_in_book_design.svg)
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;


  





  


&lt;figure class=&quot;inline-svg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;svg class=&quot;canon&quot; xmlns=&quot;http:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.w3.org&#x2F;2000&#x2F;svg&quot; overflow=&quot;visible&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 496 373&quot;
   height=&quot;373&quot; width=&quot;496&quot;&gt;
   &lt;g fill=&quot;none&quot;&gt;
      &lt;path stroke=&quot;#000&quot; stroke-width=&quot;.75&quot;
         d=&quot;M.599 372.348L495.263 1.206M.312.633l494.95 370.853M.312 372.633L247.643.92M248.502.92l246.76 370.566M330.828 123.869V1.134M330.396 1.134L165.104 124.515&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;path&gt;
      &lt;path stroke=&quot;#ED1C24&quot; stroke-width=&quot;.75&quot;
         d=&quot;M275.73 41.616h166.224v249.05H275.73zM54.478 41.616h166.225v249.052H54.478z&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;path&gt;
      &lt;path stroke=&quot;#000&quot; stroke-width=&quot;.75&quot; d=&quot;M.479.375h495v372h-495zM247.979.875v372&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;path&gt;
      &lt;ellipse cx=&quot;498.729&quot; cy=&quot;177.625&quot; rx=&quot;.75&quot; ry=&quot;1.25&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;ellipse&gt;
      &lt;ellipse cx=&quot;247.229&quot; cy=&quot;377.375&quot; rx=&quot;.75&quot; ry=&quot;1.25&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;ellipse&gt;
   &lt;&#x2F;g&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;svg&gt;&lt;!----&gt;
  
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Van de Graaf canon&lt;&#x2F;figcaption&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don&#x27;t want to display a caption below the image, you can set the Markdown image &lt;code&gt;alt&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; text to an empty string, &lt;code&gt;Inline SVG&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;inline-svg&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;, or &lt;code&gt;inline_svg&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot; style=&quot;background-color:#2b303b;color:#c0c5ce;&quot; class=&quot;language-markdown &quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-markdown&quot; data-lang=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% inline_svg() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;![](Van_de_Graaf_canon_in_book_design.svg)
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% inline_svg() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;![Inline SVG](Van_de_Graaf_canon_in_book_design.svg)
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% inline_svg() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;![inline-svg](Van_de_Graaf_canon_in_book_design.svg)
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% inline_svg() %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;![inline_svg](Van_de_Graaf_canon_in_book_design.svg)
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;{% end %}
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;
&lt;!----&gt;


  





  


&lt;figure class=&quot;inline-svg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;svg class=&quot;canon&quot; xmlns=&quot;http:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.w3.org&#x2F;2000&#x2F;svg&quot; overflow=&quot;visible&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 496 373&quot;
   height=&quot;373&quot; width=&quot;496&quot;&gt;
   &lt;g fill=&quot;none&quot;&gt;
      &lt;path stroke=&quot;#000&quot; stroke-width=&quot;.75&quot;
         d=&quot;M.599 372.348L495.263 1.206M.312.633l494.95 370.853M.312 372.633L247.643.92M248.502.92l246.76 370.566M330.828 123.869V1.134M330.396 1.134L165.104 124.515&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;path&gt;
      &lt;path stroke=&quot;#ED1C24&quot; stroke-width=&quot;.75&quot;
         d=&quot;M275.73 41.616h166.224v249.05H275.73zM54.478 41.616h166.225v249.052H54.478z&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;path&gt;
      &lt;path stroke=&quot;#000&quot; stroke-width=&quot;.75&quot; d=&quot;M.479.375h495v372h-495zM247.979.875v372&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;path&gt;
      &lt;ellipse cx=&quot;498.729&quot; cy=&quot;177.625&quot; rx=&quot;.75&quot; ry=&quot;1.25&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;ellipse&gt;
      &lt;ellipse cx=&quot;247.229&quot; cy=&quot;377.375&quot; rx=&quot;.75&quot; ry=&quot;1.25&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;ellipse&gt;
   &lt;&#x2F;g&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;svg&gt;&lt;!----&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;figure&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
